Carlos Perez

A software developer that focuses strongly on the customer experience. I specialize in designing the customer. I am well-rounded with experience designing front-end interfaces, wireframes, and interaction between pages and the back-end systems. I uniquely bring an entrepreneurial mindset and vision to any project or business.

965 Eastwind drive Placentia, CA 92870 (714) 299-6994 solracias@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Blizzard Entertainment, Irvine, CA — Software Test Analyst MONTH 2012 - PRESENT

 Improved deployment efficiency by creating a test automation framework using selenium to execute frequent smoke tests prior to deployment on production.

Zeebo inc, San Diego — QA Manager

 Reduced the number of customer complaints from 80% to 10% by implementing a structured QA department with more efficient divisions of game testing, firmware/software testing, and web testing.

Midway Home Entertainment, San Diego — Lead Test Analyst 2008 - 2009

- Reduced a large number of redundant and irrelevant bug reports from external QA groups from 80% to 7% by creating clear testing guidelines.

Crave Entertainment, Newport Beach, CA — Lead Test Analyst 2006 - 2008

- Increased certification approvals from 30% to 80% by implementing internal test reports prior to submission.

EDUCATION

University of Phoenix, San Diego, CA — GPA 3.70

2010 - 2014

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration and Entrepreneurship

UC Irvine, Irvine, CA — UC Irvine

03/2017 - expected graduation - 09/ 2017

Certification of Web Development.

Test Automation Tech Skills

C#, Selenium, MStest, Fluent assertions.

Web Development Tech Skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript, node.js, npm, MySQL, Jquery, API (AJAX), Express, Handlebars, React, MongoDB

Soft skills

Agile/scrum expertise
Mentor leadership style
Timely communication
Big-picture thinking
Willingness to learn
Business-acumen

LANGUAGES

English, Spanish